Finding aid for the Los Angeles Alliance for a New Economy records, 1987-2013 LSC.2252
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Vivian Rothstein Files, 1997-2010
  - Latest Press, (2001-2002) (Box 23)
  - LAX Argenbright election, (1999) (Box 24)
  - Legal Memos, (2000-2001) (Box 23)
  - Living Wage Next Step, (circa 2004) (Box 23)
  - Living Wage Referendums, (2001) (Box 23)
  - Loews history, (circa 2002) (Box 23)
  - Loews Hotel, (2001) (Box 23)
  - Los Angeles Living Wage General, (circa 1995) (Box 23)
  - Opposition Literature Pro KK, (undated) (Box 23)
  - Opposition Research, (2002) (Box 23)
  - Pacific Shores Card Check Committee, (1998-2000) (Box 23)
  - Pro Worker reports, commissions, hearings, (1997-2001) (Box 24)
  - Respect at LAX strategy meetings, (2000-2001) (Box 24)
  - Respect at LAX: Good Jobs for a Better LA information packet, (circa 1999) (Box 24)
  - Santa Monica current, (2005) (Box 23)
  - Santa Monica Election, (2004) (Box 23)
  - Santa Monica Living Wage Campaign, (2000) (Box 23)
  - Santa Monica Living Wage committee (2 files), (2001) (Box 23)
  - Santa Monica Living Wage fact sheets, (circa 2001) (Box 23)
  - Santa Monica Living Wage Law, (1999-2002) (Box 23)
  - Santa Monica Team (2 files), (2001) (Box 23)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) Executive Committee, (2000-2001) (Box 23)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) Living Wage Kick-Off information packet, (1999 Jun 5) (Box 23)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) meeting list, (2005) (Box 23)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) New Legislation Options, (2003) (Box 23)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) Policy Planning, (2004) (Box 23)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans United for Responsible Tourism), (1997-1998) (Box 23)
  - Truth Commission, (2002-2003) (Box 23)
  - Worker Justice: Serve It Up, (undated) (Box 23)
- Administrative Activities, 1993-2002, 2006, 2009; 1993-2002
  The series is a mix of files representing what appears to be internal LAANE operations such as meetings, retreats, training, and the original organization, The Tourism Industry Development Council (TIDC) mission-type documents. Additionally, there is an electronic hard drive containing videos, television coverage, and digitized photographs. There are also a small number of video, a DVD-R, a floppy, and CD that are LAANE and/or media created coverage of LAANE activities. There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  - 15 Years of Fighting for Justice (DVD recording), (undated) (Box 28)
  - Concept Papers TIDC (Tourism Industry Development Council) Action Plan and Organizing Project (7 files), (1993) (Box 15)
  - Insight Tours Report, (circa 1995) (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - IRS Lobbying, (undated) (Box 12)
  - LAANE (external hard drive), (undated) (Box 28)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    Videos, television coverage, and digitized photographs. Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials, please notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - LAANE 2006 Year in Review (digital betacam (digi beta) recording), (2006 Nov 28) (Box 35)
  - LAANE 2006 Year in Review (DVD recording) (Box 28)
  - LAANE Budget, (2001) (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - LAANE: Changing Lives, 2009 Awards (DVD recording) (Box 28)
  - LAANE Dinner Video (DVD recording), (2009) (Box 28)
  - LAANE Press Conference with John Edwards (CD), (2006 Nov 30) (Box 28)
  - LAANE Retreat, (2001) (Box 11)
  - LAANE: The Road to Justice (VHS recording), (2002) (Box 35)
  - Leadership Recruitment, (undated) (Box 11)
  - Living Wage Staff Meeting Notes, (undated) (Box 13)
  - Local Talk with Bill Rosendahl (VHS recording), (2002 Jul 24) (Box 35)
  - Nick Ayers, (1995) (Box 13)
    3.5 inch floppy disk labeled Non-Profit Funding Board Back-Up moved to Box 28 for preservation purposes.
  - Nick Ayers (3.5 inch floppy disk labeled Non-Profit Funding Board Back- Up), (1994 Jul 28) (Box 28)
    3.5 inch floppy disk moved from Box 13 folder 28. Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials, please notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - On Any Day: A Visit To L.A.'s Neighborhood (Betacam SP recording), (undated) (Box 34)
  - Road to Justice dub master (The) (Betacam SP recording), (2002 May 30) (Box 35)
  - Subsidy Training Land Use, (1997) (Box 8)
  - TIDC (Tourism Industry Development Coalition) meeting, (1995 Apr) (Box 13)
  - Tourism Industry Development Council (2 files), (1997) (Box 9)
  - Training Windcall Retreat Materials, (1999 Jun) (Box 8)
  - Video Press Release materials, (undated) (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Voices of Courage: Stories from the Nation's Low Wage Capital (DVD recording), (undated) (Box 28)
  - Wage and Benefit Survey of Non-Profits, (1996) (Box 12)
  - Wining and Dining Union in Los Angeles (Tourism Industry Development Council), (undated) (Box 16)
- Foundation Proposals and Reports, cira 1996 - circa 2006
  Consists of proposals, reports, and grant applications prepared by LAANE in its first 10 years of operation and submitted to a variety of private foundations. Programs include Alliance for Technology Access, California Community Foundation, and Jewish Fund for Justice, among others.
  - Aberlard Foundation, (1997-1998) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Alliance for Technology Access, (2003) (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Butler, (2002) (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - California Community Foundation, (2004-2005) (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - California Endowment, (2003) (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - California Endowment, (2001-2004) (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - California Healthcare Foundation, (2000-2004) (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - California Wellness, (2001-2006) (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Casey Foundation, (2002-2006) (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Campaign for Human Development (CCHD) National and Local, (2002-2004) (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Community Technology Foundation of California, (2001-2004) (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Discount Foundation, (1997-1998) (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Engagement Innovation Test Fund (common assets), (2004) (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - FACT (French American Charitable Trust), (2001-2006) (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Ford Foundation, (2001-2006) (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Funding Exchange, (1997-1998) (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Handleman, (1996, 1998, 2004-2006) (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Irvine Foundation, (2000-2006) (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Fund for Justice, (1997-1998) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Liberty Hill, (2002-2003) (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Liberty Hill, (2003-2006) (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Liberty Hill, (2002) (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - List Foundation, (2001-2002) (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - McKay Foundation, (2000-2006) (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - MS Foundation, (1998-2005) (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Need or Fund, (2001-2006) (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - New Voices - Academy for Educational Development, (2004) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - New World Fund, (2000-2006) (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - New World Fund, (2001-2003) (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Norman Foundation, (2002-2003) (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Ottinger Foundation, (2002-2005) (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Penny Family, (1999-2006) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, (2002-2006) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, (2003) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, (2003) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Rosenberg Foundation, (1998-2006) (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Rosenberg Foundation, (2000) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Solidago, (2003) (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Stern Family Fund, (2003) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Streisand Foundation (The), (2002) (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Tides, (2003) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Verbena Fund, (2001) (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Washington Mutual, (2002) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Women's Foundation, (1998-2006) (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Fundraising Events Publications and Programs, 2002-2013
  Consists of LAANE fundraising event publications and programs. Includes Annual Dinner Ad Books, City of Justice Awards Dinner ad books and annual Women for a New Los Angeles lunch programs.
  - Annual Dinner ad books, (2002-2006) (Box 33)
  - Annual Women's Lunch programs, (2008-2011) (Box 33)
  - City of Justice Awards Dinner programs, (2012-2013) (Box 33)
  - City of Justice Awards Dinner programs, (2010-2011) (Box 33)
  - City of Justice Awards Dinner programs, (2007-2008) (Box 33)
  - Fundraising programs and publications, (undated) (Box 33)
- Reports and Research, 1998-2013
  Consists of information reports and research prepared by/for LAANE related to Community Redevelopment Agency, Angeles Living Wage, and Santa Monica Living Wage campaigns, and other policy campaigns.
  - Airport Improvement handbook, (2004 Jan 8) (Box 33)
    Related to Respect at LAX campaign.
  - Airport Living Wage Worker surveys (2 files), (2003) (Box 33)
  - Century Boulevard Hotel Reports, (2006 Apr 25) (Box 32)
    Related to Campaign for a New Century campaign.
  - Construction Careers, (2011 Jan) (Box 32)
    Related to Construction Careers campaign.
  - Environmental and San Diego reports, (2005, 2012) (Box 32)
  - Grocery Food Access, (2008 Jul) (Box 32)
  - LA Living Wage Report, (undated) (Box 32)
    Related to Los Angeles Living Wage campaign.
  - LAANE Poverty Reports, (2007 Aug 28) (Box 32)
  - LAX Airport, (2005 Jul) (Box 32)
  - LAX Living Wage Member survey, (2007) (Box 33)
  - LAX Modernization research, (2001) (Box 33)
  - Living Wage packet, (1999) (Box 33)
  - Living Wage surveys (3 files), (2002) (Box 32)
  - Local Development, (1999 Mar) (Box 32)
    Related to Community Redevelopment Agency campaign.
  - Long Beach, (2009 Feb) (Box 32)
    Related to Long Beach Coalition for Good Jobs and a Healthy Community campaign.
  - Los Angeles Hotels, (2013 Jul) (Box 32)
    Related to Raise LA campaign.
  - Los Angeles Living Wage Report, (undated) (Box 32)
  - Nike Study Indonesia and Vietnam, (1998) (Box 12)
  - Port Trucking, (2010 Apr 15) (Box 32)
    Related to Clean Trucks campaign.
  - Repower Los Angeles, (2012 Feb) (Box 32)
    Related to Repower LA campaign.
  - Santa Monica (3 files), (2000) (Box 33)
    Related to Santa Monica Living Wage campaign.
  - Santa Monica Reports, (2003 Jun) (Box 32)
  - Security Guards, (2006 Apr) (Box 32)
  - Taking Care of Business? An Evaluation of the Los Angeles Business Team, (1999 Oct) (Box 32)
  - Waste and Recycling, (2011 Jan) (Box 32)
    Related to Don't Waste LA campaign.
- Alliances with Others, 1989, 1997-2005
  The bulk of series consists of event programs, presentation handouts, and information packets prepared by and/or related to allied organizations within and outside the Los Angeles area. Organizations represented include CAUSE (Coalitions for Accountability in the Universal Studios Expansion), Jubilee Justice Catholic Roundtable, and New York City Organizing Supports Center among others. The series is arranged alphabetically by file title.
  - Billy Bragg Event, (1999 Aug) (Box 7)
  - CAUSE (Coalition for Accountability in the Universal Studies Expansion), (1998) (Box 7)
  - CAUSE (Coalition for Accountability in the Universal Studios Expansion) notes and memos, (1998) (Box 12)
  - Charter Reform, (undated) (Box 7)
  - CHIRLA (Asociacion de Trabajodoras Domesticas de Los Angeles), (1999) (Box 7)
  - Coalition Meetings, (1997) (Box 15)
    Appears to be related to several unions.
  - Community Tourism (3 files), (1999) (Box 10)
  - County Federal Community Services Program, (2003) (Box 11)
  - Executive Summary - SAP CRA (Community Redevelopment Agency), (1999) (Box 7)
  - Goetz Wolff Class Presentation, (1999) (Box 7)
  - Housing TOT (Los Angeles City Transient Occupancy Tax) Campaign, (2000) (Box 10)
  - Immigrant Freedom Ride, (2003) (Box 11)
  - Jobs with Justice, (1999 Feb) (Box 7)
  - Jubilee Justice Catholic Roundtable, (1999) (Box 12)
  - Just Economics, (2001) (Box 8)
  - Labor Community Services Program AFL-CIO, (1999) (Box 10)
  - Living Wage Information Packet, (undated) (Box 7)
  - Mailing/Phone Lists, (1997) (Box 12)
  - Mayor's Task Force regarding 9/11, (2001) (Box 8)
  - New World Presentation, (1999 Jun 4) (Box 7)
  - New York City Organizing Support Center, (1999) (Box 7)
  - Nice Correspondence, (1998) (Box 7)
  - Price of Renewal (The) (DVD recording), (2005) (Box 35)
  - Proposition 226, (1998) (Box 12)
  - Proposition 5, (1998) (Box 7)
  - San Francisco Marriot Affirmative Action, (1989) (Box 12)
  - Subsidy/Account Presentation, (1998 Nov 20) (Box 7)
  - Tides Fund Visit Materials, (1999 Aug 25) (Box 7)
  - Veatch Presentation, (1999 Jan 10) (Box 7)
- Press Clippings, 1987-2008
  The series consists of original and photocopied press clippings representing LAANE activities and/or events of tangential interest to the LAANE organization. The series is arranged by file titles representing subject or title of article.
  - Accountable Development, (2003-2005) (Box 1)
  - Atlanta Airport Situation, (1995) (Box 2)
  - Bad News for Workers, (1995) (Box 2)
  - Big Box Ordinance, (2003-2004) (Box 1)
  - CA One Services, (1994) (Box 2)
  - California Living Wage, (1998-2003) (Box 1)
  - Century Blvd (6 files), (2006 -2008) (Box 1)
  - Century Blvd Living Wage, (1999 Mar - 2006 Jun) (Box 1)
  - City Economic Development, (1999-2000) (Box 1)
  - Community Impact Report, (2003 Aug-Dec) (Box 1)
  - Construction Campaign, (2007-2008) (Box 1)
  - CRA (Community Redevelopment Agency) Press Coverage, (1999-2003) (Box 1)
  - CRDI (Coalition for Responsible Development in Inglewood) Press Coverage, (1996) (Box 1)
  - Cultural Tourism News Articles: Video, (1995) (Box 1)
  - Development, (2008) (Box 1)
  - Displaced Worker Ordinance, (2000-2001) (Box 1)
  - Double Tree Hotel, (2001-2003) (Box 1)
  - Economy, (2001-2002) (Box 1)
  - Faith Communities, (1993-2003) (Box 1)
  - Four Points Hotel, (2002-2005) (Box 1)
  - Good Jobs, (2006-2007) (Box 1)
  - Greek Theater, (1999 Aug- 2000 Jan) (Box 1)
  - Grocery Worker Retention, (2005-2006) (Box 1)
  - Hollywood and Vine Project, (2006 Apr) (Box 1)
  - Hospital Campaign, (2007) (Box 1)
  - Hotel Workers, (1997-2005) (Box 1)
  - Hotels, (2000) (Box 1)
  - Hotels- E.C. (el Consejo de Empleadores de Hoteles de Los ngeles) Fight, (2005-2006) (Box 1)
  - Inclusionary Zoning, (2005 Jun-Jul) (Box 1)
  - Inglewood, (2005-2006) (Box 1)
  - Janitors for Justice, (2000) (Box 1)
  - LA City Council- Committee Assignment, (1995 Aug) (Box 2)
  - LAANE Op-Eds, (2005) (Box 1)
  - LAX Food Vendors Warned, (1995 Oct) (Box 2)
  - LAX Miscellaneous, (2001 Aug-Sep) (Box 1)
  - LAX Redevelopment, (1997-2006) (Box 1)
  - LAX Worker Organizing, (1997-2001) (Box 1)
  - Living Wage, (2005) (Box 1)
  - Living Wage (2 files), (2002-2003) (Box 2)
  - Living Wage and Unions, (1996-1997) (Box 2)
  - Living Wage Laws, (2001-2005) (Box 1)
  - Local Economy, (1995-2001) (Box 2)
  - Local Politics, (1996-2001) (Box 2)
  - Loews Hotel, (2000-2002) (Box 2)
  - Los Angeles/ Airport Living Wage, (1999) (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Early Living Wage, (1996-2000) (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Effects of Living Wage, (2005 Jun) (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Health Crisis, (1998-1999) (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Hotels, (2005) (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles - Inglewood, (1996) (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Living Wage (6 files), (1996-1998) (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Politics, (2006-2008) (Box 1)
  - Madeline Janis (3 files), (2002-2011) (Box 2)
  - Miguel Contreras, (2005 May) (Box 2)
  - Minimum Wage, (1999-2001) (Box 2)
  - Miramar Hotel, (1997-2000) (Box 2)
  - National, (1999-2001) (Box 2)
  - National Living Wage, (1998-2001) (Box 2)
  - North Hollywood, (2000 Dec - 2006 Mar) (Box 2)
  - Organizing, (2004-2008) (Box 2)
  - Other States Living Wage, (1999-2002) (Box 2)
  - Passenger Services Campaign, (2007-2008) (Box 2)
  - Philanthropy, (2006-2007) (Box 2)
  - Playa Vista and Other Developments, (1999 July - 2000) (Box 2)
  - the Player (LA Weekly article), (1997 Nov 28) (Box 3)
  - Ports Campaign, (2006-2009) (Box 2)
  - Post 9/11, (2001-2002) (Box 2)
  - Poverty (2 files), (2006-2008) (Box 2)
  - Poverty/Working Poor, (1997-2000) (Box 2)
  - Press Correspondence, (1996) (Box 2)
  - Prevailing Wage, (1995) (Box 2)
  - Respect at LAX, Crenshaw Development, and Walmart, (1999-2005) (Box 1)
  - Santa Monica, (1990-1996) (Box 2)
  - Santa Monica (7 files), (1987-2005) (Box 3)
  - Santa Monica City Council, (1999-2003) (Box 3)
  - Santa Monica Displace Worker Protection Law, (2001) (Box 3)
  - Santa Monica Living Wage, (1996-1999) (Box 3)
  - Santa Monica Living Wage (5 files), (1997-2001) (Box 3)
  - Secession, (2002) (Box 3)
  - Secession, (2002) (Box 3)
  - Security Guard, (2005-2008) (Box 3)
  - Security Guards Union, (2005 Sep - 2006 Apr) (Box 3)
  - Security Officers, (2005) (Box 3)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) Articles (2 files), (2002 Mar - Oct) (Box 3)
  - Staples, (2001-2005) (Box 3)
  - State, (2000-2001) (Box 3)
  - Sunquest Development Project, (1998-2003) (Box 3)
  - Superstore Ordinance, (2004) (Box 3)
  - Tesco (2 files), (2007-2008) (Box 3)
  - Unions, (1998) (Box 2)
  - Unions (2 files), (1999-2003) (Box 4)
  - Universal Project Clippings, (1998) (Box 4)
  - Universal Studios (2 files), (1998-2000) (Box 4)
  - USC, (1998-2000) (Box 4)
  - Walmart, (2003-2006) (Box 4)
  - Walmart / $.99 Stores, (2005) (Box 4)
  - Walmart Los Angeles (5 files), (1999-2004) (Box 2)
  - Walmart National, (2003-2004) (Box 4)
  - Walmart Report (2 files), (2007) (Box 4)
  - Worker Retention, (2005) (Box 4)
  - Workers' Rights, (1996) (Box 4)
  - Working Poor, (2000-2004) (Box 4)
  - Working Poor Study, (2000-2005) (Box 4)
- Photographs and Ephemera, 1995-2006, 2011, 2012; 1995-2006
  The series comprises photographs and a very small number of publicity buttons and t-shirts related to LAANE campaigns and events. Photographs include, among others, LAANE staff and volunteers, and document LAANE's early years as well as Respect at LAX, Santa Monica Allied for Responsible tourism, and the Walmart campaign in Inglewood. The buttons and t-shirts represent LAANE support for HERE Local 11 and Local 814 unions and Santa Monica Measure JJ. There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  - Arrest in Support of Grocery Workers photographs, (2004) (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Buttons in support of HERE Local 11 and Local 814 (8 items), (undated) (Box 27)
  - Century Blvd Radisson Hotel photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - City election Santa Monica photographs, (1998) (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Clergy Actions to Support Hotel Workers photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Clergy blessing Loews Workers photographs, (2000) (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Commission to Investigate 2002 Election Misrepresentation of voters photographs, (2003) (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Community Delegations to Miramar Hotel regarding treatment of workers photographs, (1997) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - CRDI (Coalition for Responsible Development in Inglewood) photographs, (1995) (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Demonstration for Viceroy Workers in Santa Monica photographs, (2003) (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - During Democratic National Convention Loew's Campaign photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Fundraiser at Stanley and Betty Scheinbaum's House photographs, (1997) (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Gigante Valley Jobs photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - HERE for Justice! T-Shirt, (undated) (Box 27)
  - Hired Anti-Living Wage Signature Gatherers photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Hollywood and Vine Community Benefit Agreement photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Holy Week Clergy Demo for Living Wage photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Hotel City Wide Contract Fight photographs, (2004-2006) (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Housekeepers Demonstration downtown and civil disobedience photographs, (2004) (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - JJ Election SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) office photographs, (2002) (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Jonathan Club Fires Workers photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Journey Toward Justice photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - LAANE Retreat photographs, (2004) (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - LAANE staff through the years photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - LAANE VIPs photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Labor in the Streets photographs, (2000) (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - LAX workers photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Living Wage Training photographs, (1997-1998) (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Loew's Hotel Settlement Press Conference photographs, (2002) (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Los Angeles Living Wage photographs, (1997) (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Madeline Janis photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Miramar Hotel Campaign photographs, (1996-1998) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Miramar Truth Commission photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - New Otani Demonstration- Dirty Laundry photographs, (2000) (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - No on KK fake Living Wage Law photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Pacific Shores Card Count at Unitarian Church photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Pictures from LAANE Fundraising Events photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Post Sept 11 Relief Centers photographs, (2001-2002) (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Preparing Testimony at Santa Monica City Hall photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Prop JJ election campaign photographs, (2002) (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Prop KK election photographs, (2000) (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Prophets in the Marketplace prop KK photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Release of LAANE poverty study photographs, (2011) (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Respect at LAX photographs, (1996-1999) (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Roxana Tynan promoted to new LAANE executive director photographs, (2012) (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Santa Monica Activists photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Santa Monica CLUE (Clergy and Laity United for Economic Justice) Procession photographs, (2001) (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Santa Monica Election Training Church on Ocean Park photographs, (circa 1998) (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Santa Monica High School Demonstration with Dolores Huerta to support Double Tree Workers photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Santa Monica Hotel Workers photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Sick-in Demonstration at Loew's Hotel for Health Coverage and Street theater Demonstration Loew's Hotel photographs, (2001) (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) Community-Sponsored Solidarity Vote for Miramar Sheraton Workers photographs, (1997 Sep 3) (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) Gets Organized photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism) Steering Committee Retreat photographs, (2003) (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied for Responsible Tourism)/LAANE house party fundraiser photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - SMART (Santa Monicans Allied fro Responsible Tourism) first fundraiser at church on Ocean Park photographs, (1999 Jun) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Superstore Ordinance photographs, (2004) (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Support Living Wage JJ photographs, (2002) (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Theology of Work workshop photographs, (1999) (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - TIDC (Tourism Industry Development Council) photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Truth Teams to KK from Ballot photographs, (1999) (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - UFCW Strike/Walkout Grocery Stores photographs, (2003) (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Universal Studios photographs, (1998) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - USC fast to support food workers photographs, (undated) (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Walmart Campaign in Inglewood photographs, (2003) (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Yes on JJ real Living Wage photographs, (2002) (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Yes on Living Wage JJ Justice Justicia T-shirt, (undated) (Box 27)